<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>[B18] Shield Generators by Frontier Developments</name>
	<targetVersion>0.18.1722</targetVersion>
	<author>JohnnyNova and Jetpack Maniac</author>
	<url>https://github.com/JonnyNova/Rimworld-Shields</url>
	<description>Version: 1.0
		Version: 1.0

		Allows for the building shield generators. Shields will stop projectiles that try to enter it but allow weapons to be fired out. This includes bullets, rockets, mortar rounds, pods of **any** variety (enemies via drop pods, cargo pods, escape pods, and yes, **your** pods). Shields have low idle power use and high power usage when stopping projectiles. Shield strength is determined from stored battery power. More batteries equals more protection.

		This was designed in keeping with the style and gameplay of Rimworld. It integrates the vanilla features and adds functionality to match the original game. It was also kept transparent in order to allow as many other mods and gameplay experiences to be had while enhancing the overall playability.

		Hook up to power net WITH batteries (shields draw instant power equal to damage received, 1 damage = 1 Wd from a battery/the power net) or else the shield will likely collapse upon being shot once.

		**Features:**
		- Existing save compatible
		- Stop projectiles (bullets, rockets, grenades, mortars, drop pods)
		- Shields use a small amount of idle power
		- Shield strength is the stored energy on your power net
		- Shields generators will heat up as the shields absorb damage and will shut off if they overheat
		- Shields come in three sizes:
		- small (3m)
		- medium (3m - 10m)
		- large (5m - 25m)
		- The small shield is minifiable and portable and contains an internal battery (1000 Wd, 50% efficient)
		- Larger shields can soak more heat before the shield collapses
		*Shields can fail if their coil temperatures get too hot and the safety is shut off (causes shorts, breakdowns, and explosions)

		**Shields Don't:**
		- Stop movement of pawns in or out of the shields
		- Stop fires
		- Heal people
		- Stop fires from explosions from propagating into the shield (Tip: don't stand near the edge if the bad guy has an incendiary launcher)

		**Compatability:**
		- No known mod conflicts

		**Optionally Supported Mods:**
		- Combat Extended (CE): Use the CE support expansion
		- RedistHeat: Cool shields with ducts


		Special Thanks to:

		JohnnyNova: Code Lead
		Jetpack Maniac: Code, documentation
		Halno: Building and UI Art:
		Morgloz: Thermal shutoff button UI used from RedistHeat (it's good, get it)
		Jaxxa: Inspired this mod from his ED-ShieldsBasic mod
	</description>
</ModMetaData>
